# MISS. KOMAL DINKAR PATIL

At Post Tasgaon, Dist - Sangli, State -Maharashtra, Pin Code - 416312 9284022812 | komal.dn.patil@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Experienced Java developer with 2 years of experience. And one month of experience as DWH/BI Developer as well. Looking forward for challenging role in your organisation where I can serve your organization and establish a career for myself.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Amdocs (Pune)

23/08/2021 - Current

Software Developer

- Interfaced with a cross-functional team of business analysts, developers and technical support professionals to determine a comprehensive list of requirement specifications.
- Analyzed requirements and designed, developed and implemented software application.
- Reworked applications to meet changing market trends and customer demands.
- Reviewed code and debugged errors, identified root cause and fixed the defects.
- · Having experience working in agile environment.

Internship - Pankaj Sir Academy (Bangalore)

01/08/2020 - 01/09/2020

Core Java Internship

Codekul (Pune)

06/06/2019 - 06/07/2019

Web Development Internship

## **EDUCATION**

Swami Ramanand Bharati Vidya Mandir, Tasgaon

2015

SSC

88.60%

Swami Ramanand Bharati jr. College Tasgaon

2017

HSC

71.38%

# PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: 04/12/1999

Nationality : Indian

## SKILLS

C

• • • •

C++

• • • •

Java

HTML

. . . .

CSS

Hibernate

• • • •

SQL

Servlet and JSP

Python

#### LANGUAGES

English

Marathi

Hindi

# Padmabhooshan Vasantraodada Patil Institute of Technology, Budhgaon

2021

B.Tech

81.3%

## **PROJECTS**

### **Amdocs - Order Management System**

- Worked on the complete order management application that automate order capture to delivery and completion.
- Implemented functionality for FE and BE as per the requirement of the
- Involved in Analysis, Design, Coding, Testing, Debugging to achieve the

# Student result management system

 Student Result Management Project which stores the student data and related part.

# **TOOLS AND IDE'S**

• Eclipse, MobaXterm, SQL Developer

#### **STRENGTHS**

- . Flexibility and willingness to take on new challenges.
- . Self motivated with a positive attitude.